我将成为环岛
I'll be the roundabout
我的话语会让你脱离尘世
The words will make you out and out
以你自己的方式过日子吧
And spend the day your way
就像清晨行驶在山谷里 听着挥之不去的回响
Call it morning driving through the sound and in and out the valley
音乐飘荡 载歌载舞
The music dance and sing
令孩子们兴高采烈
They make the children really ring
我也以你的方式过日子吧
I'll spend the day your way
就像清晨行驶在山谷里 听着挥之不去的回响
Call it morning driving through the sound and in and out the valley
在湖里及其周边
In and around the lake
崇山峻岭高耸入云 矗立于此
Mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
还有一英里我们就会见到你
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
十载夏日时光留下了我们的欢笑
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
在我邂逅爱情之前 青春逝去之前
Twenty four before my love you'll see
我会陪伴在你身边
I'll be there with you
我会将你铭记于心
I will remember you
你的剪影会牵动远方的景色
Your silhouette will charge the view of distant atmosphere
就像清晨行驶在山谷里 听着挥之不去的回响
Call it morning driving through the sound and even in the valley
在湖里及其周边
In and around the lake
崇山峻岭高耸入云 矗立于此
Mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
还有一英里我们就会见到你
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
十载夏日时光留下了我们的欢笑
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
在我邂逅爱情之前 青春逝去之前
Twenty four before my love you'll see
我会陪伴在你身边
I'll be there with you
沿着漂流的浮云 雄鹰在陆地上寻觅
Along the drifting cloud the eagle searching down on the land
乘着大风大浪 水手看见了海天相交的地方
Catching the swirling wind the sailor sees the rim of the land
雄鹰挥动的翅膀像天气一样变幻莫测
The eagle's dancing wings create as weather spins out of hand
靠近些 拥抱这大地 感觉自己不过是渺小如一粒尘埃
Go closer hold the land feel partly no more than grains of sand
我们牺牲所有不过是为了追寻人生的答案 主宰自己的命运
We stand to lose all time a thousand answers by in our hand
我们与内心深处的恐惧为邻 千万年来未曾改变
Next to your deeper fears we stand surrounded by a million years
我将成为环岛
I'll be the roundabout
我的话语会让你脱离尘世
The words will make you out and out
我将成为环岛
I'll be the roundabout
我的话语会让你脱离尘世……
The words will make you out and out...
在湖里及其周边
In and around the lake
崇山峻岭高耸入云 矗立于此
Mountains come out of the sky, they stand there
在我的青春逝去之前 我会陪伴在你身边……
Twenty four before my love and I'll be there...
我将成为环岛
I'll be the roundabout
我的话语会让你脱离尘世
The words will make you out and out
以你自己的方式过日子吧
You spend the day your way
就像清晨行驶在山谷里 听着挥之不去的回响
Call it morning driving through the sound and in and out the valley
在湖里及其周边
In and around the lake
崇山峻岭高耸入云 矗立于此
Mountains come out of the sky and they stand there
还有一英里我们就会见到你
One mile over we'll be there and we'll see you
十载夏日时光留下了我们的欢笑
Ten true summers we'll be there and laughing too
在我邂逅爱情之前 青春逝去之前
Twenty four before my love you'll see
我会陪伴在你身边……
I'll be there with you...
(旅行者的奇妙冒险)